sprintax.com 2019-06-09

# Sprintax.com | Privacy Policy

The Sprintax software has been designed, developed and is fully owned by Taxback.com.

This privacy policy sets out how taxback.com uses and protects any information you give when you use this website. Taxback.com is fully committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Taxback.com may occasionally amend this policy by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 14 February 2019. 

### What information we collect

We may collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information such as your name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * All Financial and Personal Identifiable Information pertinent to filling a tax return on your behalf

### How your information is used

We require this information to understand your needs, to provide you with a better service and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * To administer your account
  * To send you periodical marketing and promotional communications, such as emails, newsletters, SMS text messages (where you have subscribed to these services)
  * To provide the service you have requested
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We will never sell your information

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails. 

### Information Sharing

Taxback.com may disclose your information to:

  * any of our service providers including (without limitation) those engaged by us to perform functions for the processing of income tax returns;
  * persons necessary to ensure Taxback.com compliance with any applicable law, regulation, legal requirement.

Taxback.com may share your personal information only as described in this Privacy Policy. We will not sell your information. 

### Updating, verifying and deleting personal data

You may inform us of any changes in your Personal Data, and in accordance with our obligations under the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (“GDPR”) we will update or delete your Personal Data accordingly. 

Please log into your account at any time: 

  * To find out what Personal Data we hold
  * To request a copy of your personal data
  * Or to have your Personal Data updated, amended or removed from our database

You can update your personal information in your account or alternatively contact us via our website or email address. 

### Custom Audience Adverts (Facebook)

We may participate in Facebook.com's Custom Audience program. This enables us to display personalized ads to persons on our email lists when they visit Facebook.com. We provide Personal Information such as your email address and phone number to Facebook to enable Facebook to determine if you are a registered account holder with Facebook. 

To opt-out of participation in our Facebook Custom Audience, send an email from the email address you would like to opt out, to the email address provided in our contact information below. 

For your opt-out to be effective, you must: 

  * place the following text in the subject line of the email - "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads"
  * include in the body of the email your name and email address

We will then forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from all of our Facebook Custom Audience Ads. 

### Other Personalized And Behavioural Advertising Services

We may participate in additional retargeting and behavioural advertising services that will be similar to the services described above. 

You can control the placement of cookies and other data collection methodologies for the purposes of opting out. 

### Cookies and other Tracking Technologies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also helps us to improve our site. For more information on cookies, please see our [cookie policy](https://www.sprintax.com/cookie-policy.html). 

### Additional Policy Information

Our web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. We also have testimonials on our sites, for which if a user posted personal information with this, we have received permission. 

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

### Contact Information

You can contact us by writing to, telephoning us or emailing us at the address below: 

Sprintax   
333 N. Michigan Ave  
Suite 915  
Chicago IL 60601  
USA  
Tel: +353 1 887 1999 

Taxback.com  
IDA Business & Technology Park  
Ring Road  
Kilkenny  
Ireland 

Free phone: 1-866-601-5695  
Email: [info@sprintax.com](mailto:info@sprintax.com)
